Oh, Ross...
I waited so 'much.
I was dreaming about the first time you brought me here and I was afraid.
Oh, Ross...
I will not let Nampara.
Is it OK for you...
... You go away, you can return to your regiment.
But me and Jeremy?
What happened?
Ross?
Ross, what 'happened?
Something 'success.
If you do not tell me, I do not ...
Well, I will not '.
- The captain and 'out early and the lady did not and' still up. - I'm not surprised that he ruined. Still in bed at this time!
No matter, show us what 's for sale. It will not take 'a lot to choose what' we are interested.
Of 'your lady that Sir Hugh and' here to do his bidding.
Hughie?
- What do you say to that table? - Anything.
- Then nothing. - It 'a nice table, ma'am.
He could sleep under the groom. Mark the table.
Map the wing of the fireplace.
There 'a chair that you like, Hughie?
Hughie?
- Thing? - Seats. - I have a chair.
- Do not mark the chair. - That and 'a chest, lady,' more 'big chair.
- Here there 'nothing that we can really serve, Connie, we burned better in the fireplace. - So why 'we are here?
Livestock. Why 'do not you go take a look at the horses?
Are you thinking to castrated, right?
No, the puledrina.
- Daro 'a look at both. Where are the stables? - Oh ... um ...
- ... This way, lady. - Come on, Hughie?
Sir Hugh. Cosa ci fate qui?
- I came to see what you have decided. - At this hour of the morning?
I told Connie that vendevate everything and she did not want to wait. Me neither.
- Oh, it does not do anything. - I have not even started.
I mean, Ross is not 'more' in ruins.
Damn, if a man and 'ruined, and' ruined ... and also a woman.
Well, Ross is not '.
- So why 'you sell everything? - We do not sell anything.
I just bought a table.
From who?
That woman, what's her name? Right now and 'the' and is selling out to Connie your horses!
Oh, let me get down.
- Let me go up. - Not to sell the horses.
- Let's talk about above. - The lounge and 'the place to talk.
All right. First a kiss, then we talk.
Oh ok. Close your eyes.
Good morning Mrs. Poldark.
Here lady ... I sold both horses and cows.
Oh, stupid fool, 'cause you do not sell yourself?
Well, I tried.
I do not know what you said, but you and 'wrong. We do not sell anything.
It 'the house, it' horses, nothing. Ross is not 'more' in ruins. He fixed everything.
Hughie?
Well, maybe not today are ruined, but yesterday they were.
Some people do not know their place.
In my day, when you were ruined ...
... It remained ruined.
Good day, madam.
Pay no attention to her, my dear ...
- ... Just remember that you are still in debt. - For what?
You owe me a kiss ...
- ... With interest. - Hughie!
Lady, what happens?
None of your business, you go to replace everything.
Sell ​​the horses!
Before we go, then we must remain ...
- What are these things? - They make you go crazy ...
Prudie.
Prudie, look.
- What is'? - I do not know.
I do not understand what is.
- Take you. - It 's not my size. No ...
- ... And 'men, I think. - Hmm.
- Maybe the owner has bought for himself '. - Or for Jud.
There you see him with this? It would seem a radish.
- It was the Bodrugan? - They ', came to inspect.
- Demelza, what are you doing with those? - I do not know. They are yours?
Demelza, are for you. They are the latest fashion from France.
- Uh ... - they wear under clothes.
- How, where nobody sees them? - Trencrom made me know that they found Mark Daniel.
And 'in Ireland. But will 'to the Isles of Scilly to meet. The boat Trencrom part tonight. I've got to take it.
- How much will you be gone? - A week.
Leave 'cargo bay and we will keep it here.
It 's not safe, Ross.
E 'perfectly safe. Charlie Kempthorne says there 'was an assessor for months.
And 'true lady, and' pretty sure.
You have to leave their own tonight?
I have to see Mark Daniel.
I do not see him with this.
Bad weather bad times.
You can not 'change the tempo.
For everything else up to us, do and decide.
And 'what gives us' Providence.
We are stupid enough to believe it.
I guess it's Providence to make laws that put the poor in prison and leave free the rich.
Providence has made my brother Mark Daniel a murderess, not Enys.
- No, not him. - Do not you dare say a word against him. - Restrain your tongue, girl.
They were good to me, him and the lady. She told me that I can go to his house.
- You're going to marry Charlie Kempthorne. - I do not want.
You are my daughter and you do what I tell you!
- Oh, not even the old Noe 'has never seen a shower so'. - What news?
They will dock in the Bay of Nampara Saturday night.
We carry goods and hide at home. Tell Zacky.
And be careful. There are soldiers all Illogan.
- Someone must have talked. - It 'was a mistake to bring Poldark. - Oh, and 'safe enough.
Risks his skin as we do.
- And 'He helped your brother escape. - I do not trust any of them.
Phew!
This cold entered into my bones.
Should I go to the doctor.
What you need is a wife to keep you warm.
You hear that, Rosina? Charlie cold.
- Let him throw in the fire. - I'll show!
- I'll see what ends up in the fire! - No!
- No, she gave it to me! - It 'and I will burn it! - My doll!
Burns.
Bruciamoli all.
Now you will have to marry me.
I think I would have married 5 minutes after meeting you.
Thing? You were so 'cocky just' cause I asked you to look at the poor little Horace.
I never expected to marry the poor little Horace.
Caroline...
...are you sure?
It will not be 'an easy life.
But it will be 'a life with you, Dwight.
I already 'had what you call an easy life ...
... And I call an empty life.
And there 'no one to satisfy but yourself.
It becomes very difficult to meet.
Are you sure?
My love for you now and forever, and 'certain as death.
And I accepted the fact that when we are married and we went away from here ...
... I dipendero 'yourself.
This we passed it.
Caroline, I have to be honest, I will not run away like a thief.
- A small subterfuge ... - I hate the subterfuge!
If deceive others, deceive yourself.
And what will they say? That I married you for your money.
Thing?
When I give up to £ 40,000 marrying you?
Dwight.
It 's all set.
Saturday night we leave together with my coach.
- We go to London and we get married. I write to my uncle ... - Let me talk now.
And he will say 'no.
And then they will watch. And if he did not openly defy him must file 'more' word.
- As if we ... - If we run, at the time, the old gentleman is going to change 'idea and you will leave' all his money.
Potra 'seem strange ...
But I care about the old gentleman.
I do not want to hurt him.
The lighthouse 'for you ...
... But I want to do as little as possible.
Poor Dwight.
Do you want people to think well of you ...
... And not be 'so'.
Do you want everyone to be happy and they are not.
Do you want to be good ...
... But you can not.
I do not want to be good, now.
And then 'my time to go on.
You can kiss me once ... with a lot of passion.
Then you must be patient, doctor.
Mark Daniel.
I never thought you would see.
I should be dead by now. May God have mercy 'me.
You paid for this' you did.
Not in 1,000 years.
Your brother sends you his greetings. Paynter also ...
... Zacky Martin ...
...my wife.
I have a son now, Mark.
Come on, you want to drink?
Tell me what you have done in recent years.
I killed her every day since that day.
Every hour by hour.
I continued to kill millions of times.
In one country or another and 'always the same.
Do not talk to you or others, tell me about her.
- You put a tombstone? - It '... with his name, nothing else.
You should write "Killed by Mark Daniel."
- For the love of God. - For the love of God?
What do you want from me?
Whatever a dead man can do, the lighthouse 'for you.
I have to bring you back to that day when you hidden in June 'to Wheal Grace.
He said that he saw the copper. Remember?
Mark, I reopened the mine.
Henshawe and I, Zacky and others, we have explored all and nothing found.
Now, I have a bit 'of money ...
... But it will soon end.
... I have to find the copper, or there will be 'more' mine ...
... It 'work. You know what that means.
I rely on you 'cause you tell me what you saw that day, and where you saw it. Do you understand?
E 'was more' than four years ago.
- I was a little 'upset. - Well, think again.
You come down in the main shaft.
They went down into the main shaft.
There was a tunnel that led to the east. The land looked good.
And 'where we dug a new well.
There was a line of copper, but low quality ', and hardly worth the effort to extract it. It was all there '.
No, ce n'era uno grosso.
Where?
I had other things to think about. I just ...
I returned to the main shaft ...
... And I have traveled throughout its length.
I had nothing to do but wait.
Then I heard the soldiers.
Cosi 'I ... I opened the entrance of a tunnel.
I had with me a piece of candle.
I climbed up and found myself in a tunnel wide enough for the passage of a man, and deep.
I think it was just under the old strand. He dripped everywhere and rock steps were full of water.
It was dangerous ground and at the end ...
... You were there?
Mr. Francis has found the same place. And 'them dead'. He drowned.
Rest in peace.
He found the copper?
There are some clues ...
... Good clues.
You have reopened the mine because of me ...
... And this has killed your cousin.
They are a curse to all those who know me.
Guilt and 'what my anyone else. If we could predict the consequences of our actions ...
Mark, you can not continue to live under the weight of this guilt.
I pray to God ...
... Not to.
Now leave me alone. I'm not a good company for you.
Do you need something? Money?
I embark 'on Saturdays.
Do you have a message for someone?
Go to her, that I killed her, and tell her ...
"Soon".
Dwight.
Thanks, Prudie.
- I came to see Ross. - Oh, not 'here. However he will be back 'tomorrow.
It was something important?
Demelza ...
... We've known for a long time, I know I can trust you.
Dwight, there are no secrets between us.
Ross and 'went to St. Mary's, Isles of Scilly. E 'went to see Mark Daniel.
E 'for Wheal Grace. Sorry, Dwight.
But he will be back 'with the boat Trencrom tomorrow night.
They will land in the bay at midnight.
- But it 's dangerous. I saw that officer, the Scottish wandering over there days ago. - Oh, he 's pretty harmless.
Ross will 'return Sunday.
By then it will be 'party.
See, I have a secret.
Demelza ...
... I came to say goodbye.
- Tomorrow ... - going to marry Caroline Penvenen.
The sai?
Just a rabbit face peeking out of the den and everyone knows it.
Two people on horseback, well ...
Oh, Dwight, are so 'happy for you. For both.
Well, I just hope that your secret is more 'safe mine.
We will meet at midnight at the gates of Kilwarren.
We go to London and we get married.
- I will write to you'. - You'll be back, though.
I'd like to, Demelza ...
... But how can I do?
How can I ask you to live here, in a house that is' on the border of the estate of his uncle, the man we are going to betray?
No...
... And 'unthinkable.
Where will you go?
Apriro' uno studio a Londra o a Bath.
I think they 'have diseases other than here.
They suffer from the abundance, instead of lack. But I lighthouse 'my best to treat them.
Will you tell Ross and all who are here have believed me?
We entrust ourselves to you, Dwight.
You have done so 'much to help us all. This and 'your house and we love you.
Lo Terro 'semper a cashew.
But you know I do not ritornero '.
Tomorrow my life will change '.
Nothing will be 'more' the same after tomorrow.
- You stop very, captain? - No, not really. - Soon the tide changes. - Bring my bag to the ship. - Yes, sir.
It 'still upstairs?
I have already 'seen.
Mark?
Thanks, Charlie.
Have you been here quite a while ', eh?
I came to find Rosina, right?
You were nice to him, huh, girl?
That 'a good man. You do not want to miss it.
There 'escape danger.
It 'a cold night.
Cold, dark, eh, Charlie?
Too cold for me.
Too cold for guard, and this' sure.
- I think the trip will go 'smooth. - Yes'.
Are you OK?
- Did you see the doctor, right? - I saw it.
- What did he say? - She said I should stay in bed.
He said he will 'fever.
The fever?
And '.
You should not come out with us. You should be at home, in bed, like she told him.
But Jacka, I will lose 'my part if I'm not coming.
You do not worry for that.
We care for you, Charlie, you know.
As I would worry for you.
It 'kind of you, Jacka.
See you soon...
... Rosina, way.
- Then, girl, do not say hello? - See you soon.
Boar 'to see you tomorrow ...
... If you stay 'well.
Take care.
Poor old Charlie.
Should be held to if 'his fever.
And yet 'a kind man, and' came to see you.
- This will recognize him. - I do not owe you anything!
- I told you. - I do not care!
- I'll tell you what you must import! - I do not love you!
- You shall love those who will tell you 'I love! - I will not do that'! - You will do it!
War, war, nothing but war, and yet we will not be ready when it comes.
The French are gathering their army to invade, and what do we do? We gather the Parliament.
Look here.
A group of ladies parading patriotic riding in the park ...
... With red lips, white faces and noses blue.
Mr. Pitt, the well-known bachelor, say sleep with a map of Europe next to his bed.
We might expect happy events in France for the summer.
Oh, nonsense.
Uncle ...
... 'Cause you never married?
Well, my dear, not all women have pretty good assets.
Besides this', I took care of you in the last 20 years.
- If I had accepted Mr. Trevaunance ... - No, no, you were right to leave him.
You deserve a better man.
If you know a better man ...
... And so sposassi ...
... We would always come to see you, to be with you ...
...if you want it.
Of course it will be 'so', my dear. Nothing would give me more 'happy to have you here.
And I want you to bring all my pronipotini with you.
Dear Uncle Pen.
You do not call me more 'so' since you were little, Caroline.
I'm an old selfish to keep you here, away from all the entertainment you you young.
Theater, dancing, horseback riding in the park.
Oh, I do not want those things.
At the end of the month we will go on to London and we will be a bit 'uncle William and his family.
I owe him a visit ...
... And you'll have the city 'at your feet.
I have several old friends who would be more 'than happy to receive Miss Caroline Penvenen.
Please, Uncle, do not make plans for me.
- Why 'no, my dear? - Please, uncle.
I know how you hate London.
You stay here, happy and healthy, close to your fireplace.
E tu, Caroline?
I'll stay 'with you until' I can.
And then forget all the promises I made ...
... And all the hopes he had for me ...
... And what comfort I could be for you.
Remember Caroline ... who loves his Uncle Pen.
What do you say?
I made my will, my dear.
Not gonna change 'now.
Sara 'all yours.
I did not think to your will.
I was doing my.
Rosina.
Rosina, what 'happened?
Come ...
...sit here.
He bows his head forward.
... Force pulled up.
Who did so '?
Mhm?
Rosina, you must tell me.
My father.
Why'?
'Cause I said I did not want to marry Charlie Kempthorne.
He hits you like that?
Where is he now?
E 'went down' to the beach with the other. Tonight comes the boat.
Sure.
And just 'I came out, I ran away. I went all the way to race.
I was going to Kilwarren, but it 's too far.
'Cause just the'?
'Cause the lady said I could.
There 'some other place you can go? From someone Sawle?
Rosina, Miss Penvenen and I leave tonight.
I have to leave soon. How about Zacky Martin? It 'a good man.
E 'with others.
So who 'remained in Sawle tonight?
The women. But they will not enter for fear of their male relatives.
There is nobody. No one but Kempthorne.
'Cause he's not' the beach?
And 'sick, has a fever, you know.
No, I did not.
He says you told to stay at home ...
- ... Otherwise it would go down 'to meet the captain. - Captain Poldark?
Rosina, are you sure?
Who said so '? He had seen?
- I heard him say so '. - Why'?
'Cause he lied to not participate tonight?
Rosina, what will they do?
- They will carry the goods to Nampara. Let me come with you. - They talked about the soldiers?
Charlie said that he has seen, for Illogan. Oh, let me come with you.
You will be with me until Sawle. There 's hardly the time.
- You have to go home to your father. - Oh, no, I do not want ... - Hurry up. Rosina, you have to go there. Come with me, come on.
Kempthorne!
Kempthorne, open the door!
Let me in, Kempthorne!
You can not enter. I have a fever.
I'm Dr. Enys, Kempthorne. Open the door.
Otherwise it will wake up 'around the village, so' will hear what I have to say.
Check.
He sent someone 'cause I'm sick?
You are not ill, Kempthorne.
Still you do not have a fever.
You lied to find an excuse not to go with the others. Why'?
What will happen'?
I sweated with fever.
Sweat with fear.
You have been discovered.
You know what's gonna happen 'tonight. What '?!
Next, I have no time to waste on you.
They are the soldiers, right?
Not to Illogan ...
... Are Nampara!
- How should I know? - 'Cause you told them to go'.
I am a man of Trencrom.
I never laid a trap for him.
This you would, if well paid.
Reply !!
You are crazy.
Crazy, 'cause you like Rosina Hoblyn.
As the other girl, Daniel Keren.
And I'd get Rosina.
If you gain a little 'extra money ...
... Who know '?
I do not tell.
And you'll have trouble speaking with his throat cut.
There are soldiers in Nampara.
It will take many.
- Even your friends. - There will be 'more' for those who remain.
You do not have a chance, Doctor.
I already 'killed a man and not' a terrible thing.
When they find the body ...
... I'll tell him 'it was you to say to the soldiers.
All in all, and 'fortunate that you came here.
Oh ... oh, my leg!
I broke my leg, doctor.
Doctor!
- The boat and 'late. - E 'anchored behind the cape, I think.
- I can not see anything. - There should be a man on top of the cliff.
And that 'the location of Charlie. Is sick.
It 's not the only one who is sick tonight.
Here comes the boat.
Soldiers !!!
Soldiers !!!!
Remate, dammit, paddle!
Get off, you.
Raised the anchor, set sail.
Let's go away!
Via!
- Betrayed. - They ruined. - Until 'and' still dark we must try to reach safety.
Do you feel the force, Captain?
Let's go to the other side of the headland to lose them. We part so 'can not take everyone.
Come on, we know what to do. Come on, Captain.
May God be with you!
- Ah, damn the man who lit the fire. - Do not worry, sir, we'll get him.
I wanted the smugglers, not a handful of poor people.
- A man reached the beach, sir. - Oh, I think it's the last man I want to see behind bars.
They are all strangers, sir. These Cornish are all strangers.
There and 'came to mind, Sergeant, that here you are the foreigner?
Next ...
You'll get what you deserve!
Arrenditi!
Damn, let me!
- Do not you understand? What time is it? - Time? - Yes'!
It's almost six.
- And I do not think you'll need to know the time for the next two years. - We have to take away the prisoners, sir? - Not yet.
- Have you got ...? - Not your Captain Poldark, if and 'him think that, but we will.
I know where he intends to go into hiding.
Well, Sergeant, gather your men.
The boat and 'left off. I think the captain is still on board.
- Who else did you see? - Soldiers.
- Where? - Everywhere. And the majority were on this side.
If I were you, I would not bet a dime on his chance 'to get by.
Lady.
Ross, oh, sei a casa. Sei fradicio!
Master, there are soldiers, they are coming here.
- I have to hide. - The storage room.
Jud come to help us.
Careful. Done.
- Sollevalo. - Prudie.
Floor.
Oh, good Lord, protect us.
Oh, we're just ... just small sinners.
- You have no right ... - I have every right. Your husband and 'a wanted criminal.
- My husband and 'in Truro and you will have to give an account of your behavior. - Rummage the house and put a man on guard in every room. - Upstairs!
- You do not enter the room of my child! - Each room!
And take the wounded prisoners in here. Come with me.
- Wounded? - Yes'.
If you want to make you useful, you can take care of them.
What have you done? You shot the poor innocent men who have not ever hurt?
Poldark lady, one of my men and 'was killed, another 7 or 8 wounded.
My plan and 'was messed up by a careless gentleman and I have been up all night ...
... And apparently you too, so I'm not in the mood to listen to your protestations of innocence.
I know that Captain Poldark and 'here.
I told you, and 'in Truro.
I saw less than an hour ago, and you too.
Come on, lady, be reasonable.
Tell me where is' and avoid any more trouble and perhaps more bloodshed.
Okay, I'll be 'reasonable.
You're just doing your duty, and I was just doing my for my husband.
Captain Poldark not 'in Truro.
Lady.
Ah ... so 'better.
Oh, and do not 'an evil man, but he has little respect for the law.
Well, get it over with. Where '?
A St. Ives.
That the Devil take you, ma'am.
The Devil and 'Cornish and take' you first.
You, them ', come back here.
- What's your name? - In a minute I'll remember '.
- My men will they do remember now. - Jud Paynter! - Ahh ... Jud Paynter.
Where 'your master, Jud Paynter?
- The young or the old? - Still tricks. The old.
Ahhh... in Paradiso.
Before your Honor you ask me, the young ...
... And 'in his cot, he is sleeping like a baby.
Where 'Captain Poldark?
Ah, the middle?
It can 'be in one place or another. It 'on earth,' below.
You ', I've said enough, old fool.
Hey, you can not treat my house as if it were your own.
Oh yes'? I can not, ma'am?
Well, as you see, I'm doing it. And lighthouse 'here my Headquarters. You bring me a chair.
No, put it ...
...the'.
You can not treat as stupid a Scotsman.
Here and here are rest until 'do not take that man.
I ', well, now berro' that glass of wine, ma'am, if you please.
Dwight, are you okay?
Ross?
Is fine.
Thank God.
- E tu e Caroline?
- Lei...
- ... Will understand '. I pray that God understands. - Lady.
We have been betrayed.
- They knew everything. - Do not worry.
The captain ... they also know him?
I do not know. Maybe not.
There were Jud, Zacky, I ...
- Charlie Kempthorne.
- Shh...
Prudie ...
... Bring me a bowl of cold water.
What should you do you will '.
There are soldiers all Nampara.
They took Paul Daniel ...
Will Nanfan...
Ned Bottrill ...
Whitehead Scobey ...
Ted Garkick...
Pally Rogers...
Dr. Enys.
Oh, no.
And 'he was to light a fire that put us in alarm, I think.
And the captain?
Non lo so.
But it 's already serious' so'.
I spoke with one of the soldiers.
He told me...
... Who had heard everything from an informant.
Did he say anything?
Not a word.
But that says it all.
We'll leave it at Trencrom or settle it by themselves?
No, men Trencrom are gone. Our we have been captured.
It's up to us to judge.
- At the old way? - Yes'...
... The old fashioned way.
To mark time and to give him a fair trial.
Those who want to testify against Kempthorne, have until in the middle 'of the candle.
Those who want to speak on his behalf, have the other half '.
For the opinion ...
... If the candle is consumed to the water ...
... He 's innocent.
If you turn off before ...
... And 'guilty.
God is the judge.
Who speaks first?
Rosina.
No, girl, do not be afraid. I was unfair to you.
Tell 'em what you told me.
Charlie said he had a fever, but it was not true.
My father beat me and I ran to the doctor, and he said he had not seen Charlie ...
... And that was in Sawle with me.
How can 'hold out?
Non te lo so dire.
We expect.
Demelza ...
... And 'impossible that it takes much longer.
There 'no law that says What' impossible.
If there was a law, it would violate the Ross.
Captain McNeil ...
- The man who was shot in the leg must be taken to the hospital. - Oh, I will, 'Ms.
And if it is' too late? If you have to cut off his leg?
It 's not my responsibility'.
Captain Poldark and 'here. You tell me where is' and I'm leaving.
If you so 'sure it's here,' cause you take it?
You show me where you hide and I will '.
You want me to betray my own husband.
You have tried to make fun of me, mademoiselle Demelza, and that I will not lose.
Now I will show you 'who among us and' the stupid.
That 'your duty, I suppose.
- No, and 'my pleasure. - Well, to hell with your pleasure!
- This is not 'a language suitable for a lady. - I was not talking to the ears of a gentleman.
May. May!
The soldiers had surrounded us.
They knew the time, knew the place.
They knew they were going to Nampara, later, to see the captain. Who could have told them everything ', eh?
- Only Kempthorne! - Yes'. you '... - Who had a bag full of gold?
- Solo Kempthorne!
- Si', si'...
- Kempthorne!!!
I beat my daughter 'cause she did not want to marry him.
That rat.
Anyone else want to speak?
The time and 'almost finished.
Who wants to speak in his favor?
Then let them speak in his defense. Bring him to the table.
Man walks of your life.
I do not know anything.
They are innocent.
Speak, man. Where did you get the gold?
Innocent.
You have nothing to say?
They are innocent.
So it is'.
So it is'. It was me.
So be it.
Damn traitor!
I curse you, for your sake and my man 'was caught!
Whatever we will do and 'not enough for him!
Who will feed 'my children right now who have taken my husband?
- You Judas! - Leave him alone!
What will be 'fact' enough.
The old way.
Zacky when he made the sign ...
... Cut the wick straight.
Come, daughter.
- Lord. - What do you want?
I carried the wounded on the bandwagon, sir.
- If we get to camp before dark, we should leave now, sir. - We will start when I say so.
Yes, sir.
- Just ... - Just anything, Sergeant.
Prudie ...
... The captain will have 'hunger when he returns to St. Ives. Go to prepare dinner.
Stay where you are!
You think you're clever, but I know that you are not.
You think you're saving Poldark, but I tell you that you could even kill him.
Maybe 'already' in his grave.
You think you have me fooled, but the only ones who have teased you are.
Prudie ...
... When you go into the kitchen ...
... Preparing a warmer for the master's bed. The ride from St. Ives and 'long and cold.
Sergeant!
Lord?
Bring two men and two guards for a prisoner and get ready to march.
Lord.
You two, upstairs!
Sollevatelo.
Lift tables.
Captain Poldark, you should come on now!
Ross.