Mr. Culbertson? Mr. Culbertson.
Listen to me.
We'll give you one last chance
to save your worthless life.
Do you wish to die?
We're going in for a closer look.
It is no use, Taz. Finish it.
He wasted our time. Kill him now.
Get on your feet.
On your feet.
What's wrong with you, huh?
- Who are you?
- I'm Navy SEALs.
- You know how to use this?
- I'm a diplomat.
Point and shoot. Let's go.
Let's go, let's go.
My leg.
Following in his father's footsteps
as a Naval aviator,
Lieutenant Commander
Harmon Rabb Jr.
Suffered a crash while landing
his Tomcat
on a storm-tossed carrier at sea.
Diagnosed with night blindness,
Harm transferred to the Navy's
Judge Advocate General Corps,
which investigates, defends
and prosecutes the law of the sea.
There, with fellow JAG lawyer
Major Sarah MacKenzie,
he now fights in and out
of the courtroom
with the same daring and tenacity
that made him a top gun in the air.
Undersecretary of State
Lawrence Culbertson
was rescued last night
from Hamas terrorists.
A Lt. Curtis Rivers, platoon
commander from SEAL Team 7,
got Culbertson out single-handedly.
- Attention on deck.
- As you were.
Leave it to the SEALs.
A worthy sentiment, commander,
since they are the most effective
strike force in the world.
Absolutely, admiral.
Apparently, the president
agrees with me.
He asked the Secretary of Navy
to nominate Lt. Rivers
for the Medal of Honour.
That must have been
one hell of a rescue, sir.
Culbertson's the president's point man
in the Middle East peace talks.
Rivers saved him without regard
for his own personal safety
and accounted
for eight enemy casualties.
Anyway, SECNAV
wants JAG to determine
Not just the incident, major.
The president wants assurance
there is nothing
in Lt. Rivers' past
that might cause embarrassment.
To Lt. Rivers or the president?
Lt. Rivers and his men
have returned
to the Naval Special Warfare Centre,
Coronado.
You will find him on instructor detail.
All of us to California?
Unless you have other plans.
No, sir.
Good. I expect
a full and fair evaluation.
Ignore the politics.
And remember, you need testimony
from two eyewitnesses.
Dismissed.
Aye, aye, sir.
And don't let the fact that
I'm a former SEAL
influence your decision.
- No, sir.
- Absolutely not, sir.
JAG headquarters, this is...
We just got our orders, Harriet.
We leave in a few hours.
I know it wrecks our plans.
I'm gonna miss you too.
I can't wait to get back.
Really?
No. It's just that I've heard
that stiletto heels
can be bad for your ankles.
I'll get right on that,
Captain Harwich.
I didn't know Bruce Harwich
wore stiletto heels.
Sir, did you know that
the first Navy SEAL who won
the Congressional Medal of Honour
was Senator Bob Kerrey?
Did you know
that you're beet red right now?
You know, he wasn't a senator
when he received the medal.
He was a lieutenant, JG, sir.
Nice diversion, Bud.
Yeah, he lost a leg leading a SEAL raid
against Viet Cong snipers,
but was still able to direct
a counterattack which... Yes, sir?
Get on the computer and pull up
everything you can on Lt. Rivers.
- Let's see who we're dealing with.
- Aye, aye, sir.
I spoke with the Secretary of the Navy
personally about Lt. Rivers.
So why is the Judge Advocate
General Corps involved in this?
This is strictly routine, sir.
My guess is that the SECNAV
is routinely covering his butt.
Well, we have no knowledge
of that, sir.
Do you folks believe in heroes?
Yes, sir.
I suppose so.
I never did.
When soldiers shoot at each other, l...
It usually means that I've failed.
But this man, this Lt. Rivers,
he risked his life to protect me.
He never hesitated,
he never doubted.
He just stood there in the line of fire,
shooting back,
and then he carried me to safety.
He didn't even know me.
That's a true hero.
Navy beans and GI gravy
Gee, I'm glad I joined the Navy
Two-sixteen.
Halt. Good job.
Ditch your helmets.
Get on your covers. Hurry up.
Come on, move it.
Look sharp. Quickly.
Class, left face.
Log bridges. Let's go, let's go.
Go, go, go.
Get them up, ladies.
Get them up, get them up.
Hurry up. Ready.
Begin.
Any of you little kittens wanna quit?
No, sir.
I've got cocoa and cookies
for anybody who wants to cash in
their chips and ring the bell.
I've got cake for the officers.
- Anybody?
- No, sir.
What do you think this is? GI Jane?
No, sir.
Do you wanna stay and fight?
Hoorah, sir.
- Let me hear you.
- Hoorah, sir.
A SEAL must focus on a mission,
must accomplish his goals
regardless of his injuries.
The pain, the heat, the cold.
We're here to train your minds
as well as your bodies.
Your mind can teach your body
how to function.
Your strength is not in your muscles,
it's in your brains.
In your brains.
Why don't you get your brains to get
your legs to do another five laps?
Let's go.
- Move it. Let's go.
- Move it. Move it.
- Hurry up. Let's go. Hurry up.
Hurry up, ladies.
Left face.
About time.
- GI grits and GI gravy
- Lt. Rivers.
GI grits and GI gravy
I'm Lieutenant Commander Rabb,
JAG.
Major MacKenzie.
Lieutenant JG Roberts.
We'd like to talk to you.
Do I have to talk back, sir?
Bronze Star for heroism
in Panama.
Freeing a CIA operative in a daring
raid on the Carcel Modelo prison.
And a letter of instruction
for disrespect
toward a superior
commissioned officer.
Nominated for the Navy Cross
for bravery
in capturing an Iraqi oil platform
in the Gulf during Desert Storm.
Denied the Cross
and issued a warning
for violating an order
on the same mission.
If a brother improvises,
especially a brother who's a mustang,
he gets written up.
If a white boy from the academy
does the exact same thing,
he's showing individual initiative.
A brother?
An African-American.
A black man. A negro.
Don't play the race card with us,
lieutenant.
Let's get
a couple things straight, major.
One, I don't play.
And two, I'm just stating the facts.
Speaking of facts, lieutenant,
I didn't get much
out of your After Action Report
on the mission in Lebanon.
The information was sketchy at best.
Some write, I fight.
You care to tell us
what happened that night?
I rescued
an Undersecretary of State.
Any details?
I'll leave that up to you, commander.
Perhaps you don't understand
our assignment.
You wanna make sure
I'm not an embarrassment.
The first thing
the two of you asked me
was about the dings
in my service record.
I know all about the Navy
and its lawyers.
You don't know about us, lieutenant.
And quite frankly,
you're not helping your cause any.
I don't have a cause, commander.
I just do my job.
I let you pencil pushers do yours.
The Navy Cross
won't make me a better SEAL.
Lieutenant, you're not up
for the Navy Cross.
You've been nominated
for the Medal of Honour.
For conspicuous gallantry
and intrepidity
above and beyond the call of duty.
What's the real reason?
The president believes
you've earned it.
Chief, we need to debrief you
about the night
Undersecretary Culbertson
was rescued.
- I'll tell you what I know.
- That would be refreshing.
Lt. Rivers
not much of a talker, ma'am?
Tell us what happened that night.
Okay. We came ashore
in two Zodiacs.
And we left them
at the insert-extract point
and proceeded south
to an observational rally point,
about 300 yards from where
the hostage was being held.
We were there for recon.
A Ranger team was tasked
with the rescue,
and they were due in ten minutes.
What happened
to change the mission, chief?
Lt. Rivers believed Culbertson
was in imminent danger.
The Rangers hadn't shown up yet,
so the lieutenant decided
to do a closer recon on the building.
He took Douglas with him.
Douglas got hit.
The lieutenant went in on his own.
Is that standard procedure?
There is nothing standard about
the lieutenant's procedures, ma'am.
It's getting hot out here.
Why don't we go inside?
My wife's making some lemonade.
Did you see Lt. Rivers
pull Culbertson out?
No, sir. We were taking fire
from the sentries.
They had my full attention.
We've got company, honey.
Be right there.
- Please.
- Thanks.
So, what do you think about
what the lieutenant did, chief?
He's the real deal SEAL, sir.
So you admire him?
Lieutenant is a result-oriented
person, ma'am.
Is that good or bad?
The men are often
challenged by his orders, sir.
Well, isn't that his job to test you?
To keep you combat-ready?
The lieutenant likes to improvise.
Isn't that what SEALs
are trained to do, improvise?
No, ma'am.
No, you plan your dive
and you dive your plan.
A year and a half ago,
we lost our explosives man in Angola.
It didn't have to happen.
Six months ago during
downed-pilot training in Nevada,
three members of our team
were injured rappelling into a ravine.
You don't like the lieutenant,
do you, chief?
The lieutenant and I
have never socialized.
Does that answer
your question, sir?
So how does it feel to be taking orders
from an African-American, chief?
Anybody thirsty?
I'm used to that, sir.
Commander Rabb, Major MacKenzie,
my wife, Sandy.
- Hi.
- Hello.
You see, commander,
I don't object to Lt. Rivers
because he's black.
I object to him
because he gets people killed.
Commander Rabb.
Major MacKenzie.
Jon Barrow,
special assistant to the president.
It's good to meet you.
How is the investigation going?
Well, we don't have enough
information to form an opinion yet, sir.
Well, that's a politician's answer,
commander.
Is there a problem?
Not that we know of.
We just wanna be thorough.
I support that.
The lieutenant's an African-American.
It's important he be afforded
fair treatment.
- As should a man of any colour, sir.
- Agreed.
But keep in mind, in World War II,
433 Medals of Honour were awarded
but none to African-Americans.
Until the current administration.
That's correct.
Fifty years after the fact.
Mr. Barrow, you are not suggesting
we make up for past discrimination
by awarding the medal to someone
who hasn't earned it, are you?
Commander, the president believes
that awarding the medal to a minority
would promote national healing.
It would help bring us together.
For a good photo op.
GI dressed for GI training
Gee, I'm glad I joined the Navy
Mind if we join you, lieutenant?
Come for the meat loaf?
It's my favourite.
I've already told you everything
you need about me.
Okay, let's talk about the meat loaf.
I bet it's a hell of a lot better
than the MRE's in Desert Storm.
You led the SEAL diversion
at Mina Saud, didn't you?
They came up in Zodiacs,
swam to shore.
Laid C-4 down along the beach.
Man, you must have been close
enough to the Iraqis to smell them.
Yeah, one of them
almost stepped on my head.
They detonated the plastique.
First, we planted buoys in the water.
As if you were marking the way
for landing craft?
Right.
When that C-4 went off,
the Iraqis thought we were doing
an amphibious landing.
And then Stormin' Norman
took the troops
and the armour right over ground.
It was great.
So it was all a feint?
Right.
Just like the three of you pretending
to love my sea stories.
Just trying to make conversation,
lieutenant.
You got something to ask me,
then ask it.
All right.
How do you get along
with Chief Wilkins?
That's between us.
Do you want this medal, Rivers?
It's just a trinket.
You know,
General Patton once said
he would sell his soul
for the Medal of Honour.
General Patton wasn't a SEAL.
We don't do what we do
for the ribbons, ma'am.
Men die for their buddies.
Others die for their country.
And some die for no reason at all.
But no one, no one I know,
ever died for a medal.
Excuse me.
Let's go, ladies,
up and down, up and down.
Come on, hurry up.
Let's go. Get up. Get up, get up.
Rolling.
Rolling. Rolling. Rolling.
Let's go. Roll, roll here.
Back in the water.
Let's go.
It would be helpful if you moved
once in a while, lieutenant.
What's going on?
That's Leonard Kress
from World Update Magazine.
The lieutenant is the subject
of a photo essay.
Kind of a day-in-the-life diary
of a battle hero.
The thing is he's not very animated.
I wouldn't ask him to smile.
We're not even sure
those muscles work.
Hurry up. Hurry up, hurry up.
Out of the water. Out of the water.
Let's go, let's go. Hurry up.
Go, go, go. Hurry up, hurry up.
They got your sister, puke.
They're doing nasty things to her.
You're the only one who can save her.
Save her.
Come on, save her.
No, this crab's got a soft shell.
Throw him back in a pot
and we'll have him for dinner.
Skeevers, don't do it.
Simon, get back with your class.
He's no longer a member of this class.
Catch up. Hurry up.
Put your legs in the air.
- Hurry up.
- Well, that's not gonna play.
Let's go. Hurry up. Come on.
Hurry up, hurry up. Come on.
What's going on?
There were sentries on the roof
of the building,
and I took a hit in the gut.
Are you gonna be all right?
I lost 6 feet of my large intestines,
ma'am.
I'm gonna have to wear a bag
and eat Cream of Wheat
for the rest of my life.
Petty Officer Douglas,
we are looking for confirmation of
Lt. Rivers' actions during the rescue.
I'm afraid I can't help you, sir.
Why is that?
Because I didn't see
the lieutenant's actions,
other than he took out a guard
and entered the building.
Then I got hit.
And after that,
I didn't see anything else.
Next thing I know, Chief Wilkins
was bending over me in the boat.
How do you feel about Lt. Rivers?
Lt. Rivers is the leader
of my team, sir.
Do you have an opinion about whether
he deserves the Medal of Honour?
Well, as far as I'm concerned,
there were no heroes that night.
We're looking for details,
Petty Officer Hannah.
There are gaps in our understanding
of the events.
I'll do what I can, sir.
Did you witness Lt. Rivers
rescue Undersecretary Culbertson?
No, sir, I did not.
I thought SEALs
were trained to be observant.
Yes, ma'am.
We're also trained to be smart.
Are you saying
Lt. Rivers wasn't smart?
I'm saying Lt. Rivers was stupid.
In what way?
What happened that night?
Lt. Rivers was listening
to the kidnappers
through a parabolic mike.
We're going in for a closer look.
Lieutenant, the Rangers will be here
in ten minutes.
The hostage will be dead by then.
We're going in.
Our mission is recon,
not rescue, sir.
I changed our mission.
You got a problem with that?
That's affirmative.
We are not prepared for rescue.
We're prepared
if I say we're prepared.
We've got no plan, no backup.
This is my plan, this is my backup.
Your plans get people killed.
What did you say?
With all due respect, sir,
changing this mission now
is reckless and irrespon...
Tell that to the man inside
who's gonna be executed.
We don't know that for sure.
Are you refusing to obey my order?
No, sir.
- Douglas.
- Aye.
You and I are going up
to the building to recon.
The others will stay here
for cover and backup.
- Move it out.
- Roger.
By attacking the building,
Lt. Rivers revealed our presence.
He also endangered the hostage.
But if he believed
Culbertson was about to be killed...
Culbertson was a valuable hostage.
Why would they suddenly kill him?
So the lieutenant acted recklessly?
Yes, ma'am.
That's what I've been saying.
- Thank you, petty officer.
- You're welcome, sir.
As you were.
We're trying to reward someone
for needlessly endangering his men?
It's only one man's testimony, Mac.
Yeah, but it's the only testimony
we've got.
- Aye, aye, sir.
- What are you doing?
Move it, move it, move it. Come on.
What is your problem, mister?
What is your problem?
You make me sick.
You are the sorriest bunch of pukes
I have ever had the misfortune
to have to train.
Why don't you go
join the Coast Guard?
Well, not your typical
medal-winning personality.
Lt. Rivers' medal
is in serious jeopardy, Bud.
He may not only lose the medal.
He could very well be facing
a charge of dereliction of duty.
Ambulance chasing?
Social call.
Well, I would venture a guess,
lieutenant,
that you have never been married.
If the Navy wanted me
to have a wife,
they would have issued me one
with my dog tags and my seabag.
Being the wife of a Navy SEAL
is no picnic.
All the separations,
they don't know where you are.
Doesn't promote
a real close relationship.
I saw what it did to my parents.
I don't want no part of it.
My dad, he loved the Navy.
Never made it
above the rank of seaman.
That's him in the middle.
Seaman Edgar Rivers.
Would have made
one hell of an officer.
Never made it out of the galley.
Do you know, in the history
of the United States Navy,
there wasn't a black officer
until near the end of World War II?
Yeah, the Navy's making up for that.
Yeah, a little too late for my father.
He lived and breathed the Navy.
Until he died. He died in the brig.
Busted in rank and broken in spirit.
What was the offence?
Someone stole some money
out of the officer's wardroom.
They blamed my pop.
Court-martialed him.
He hanged himself in his cell.
I'm sorry.
Six months later, a white bosun's mate
admitted to the crime
after being busted
doing the same thing on another ship.
JAG officer prosecuted my father.
Another one defended him.
Neither one of them believed him.
Well, that explains why you feel
the way you do about Navy lawyers.
I was just a toddler at the time.
I don't really remember much.
But I did read the letters
that he wrote my mom
while he was in prison.
No bitterness.
Not one shred of hate in the man.
He must have had a big heart.
He did.
It doesn't run in the family, though.
Strangers in the night
Exchanging glances
Wondering in the night
That is so sweet.
Harriet?
What? I can't hear you.
It's Bud Roberts Jr.
Let me call you later
when I get to the room.
I miss you.
Me too. Bye.
- Machine?
- Yeah.
Excuse me,
could I get another pineapple?
- Sure.
- Three in one night.
You surprise me, Bud.
I'm drowning my sorrows, ma'am.
You got it bad, lieutenant.
Permission to speak freely, ma'am?
Look at the black kettle
calling the pot the same thing.
I am not lovesick, Bud.
You called the commander Dalton.
I did not.
Yes, you did. Twice.
I can't believe
he didn't say anything.
I think he's just afraid
of losing you, ma'am.
You're leaving JAG,
aren't you, ma'am?
No one's offered me
anything yet, Bud.
What if they do?
Excuse me.
- Where are you going?
- I'm going to the thing.
I'd like to dedicate this to
the most important woman in my life.
I saw the light on the night
That I passed by her window
I saw the flickering shadows of love
On the blind
She was my woman
As she deceived me
I watched and went out of my mind
My, my, my, Delilah
Why, why, why, Delilah
You know, I would have...
I would have thought
you were a cigar man.
I would be if they didn't
taste like goat patties.
I like them. Goat patties.
Well, if they could roll
a bottle of Jack in a tobacco leaf,
it would be a different story.
You know, my mother used to say
that stars were holes poked
in the black curtain of night.
It was God's way of letting us know he
was watching us from the other side.
That's kind of nice.
Yeah.
I did most of my killing at night.
I guess it didn't have
much influence, huh?
Lieutenant, I'm gonna be
honest with you.
One of your men has accused you
of endangering the team and
the hostage the night of the rescue.
He claims you were out of control
and acted without discretion.
You must think you've got me drunk
enough to answer your questions.
He blames the casualties
on your inadequate leadership skills.
I'm giving you an opportunity
to defend yourself.
The truth shall not set us free.
If you actually believe that,
then I pity you.
Look, it's going to take a lot
more than cigars
and bourbon and your pity
to get anything out of me.
Oh, yeah? What would it take?
Do you know the secret to happiness,
commander?
Not yours, I don't.
Then I can't help you.
I don't know but I've been told
Eskimo women are mighty cold
Admiral, I can't
squeeze it out of him.
Without Lt. Rivers' account
of the events,
I have to rely
on the testimony of his men.
- Which is damning?
- Yes, sir.
And if you had to make
a decision now?
I'd cancel medal considerations
and proceed with an investigation
into misconduct in the field.
Look, commander,
the SECNAV is getting pressure
from the White House.
He's expecting us
to give him some relief.
I understand that, sir.
We're feeling it here too.
Well, there's gotta be
another way in.
The lieutenant is a hard case, sir.
He has zero support.
With the exception
of Undersecretary Culbertson.
The man saved my life,
for God's sake.
I'm sorry if his men
were put in danger,
but correct me if I'm wrong,
isn't it a dangerous job?
- Damn straight.
- So, what's the problem?
There seems to be some concern
about Lt. Rivers' behaviour in the field.
It's extremely rare for a SEAL team
to publicly question one of their own,
especially their superior.
Are you saying that
the lieutenant is not worthy?
His men have raised
serious questions.
Was the lieutenant in control?
Was his attitude acceptable?
Was he correct
in changing the mission?
Yes, I would say, selfishly.
Here.
I understand how you feel, sir,
but if the lieutenant
is to be awarded this medal,
I need more than just your gratitude.
For example?
You were the only eyewitness
to the rescue.
Can you remember anything else
about it?
Anything in particular?
Any details
you may have overlooked.
What do you remember about
what went on after the firefight?
Well, after the lieutenant
brought me out of the building,
he hid me behind some rocks,
and then, when he came back, he...
Wait a minute.
Came back from where?
I don't know.
I saw this big red flare,
and then he reappeared
and he carried me out of there.
Did Lt. Rivers send up a flare
after Culbertson's rescue?
Yes, sir. A red pop-up.
Thanks. Why?
That was to notify us
of Petty Officer Douglas' position.
Douglas was down?
Yes, sir.
So the lieutenant took responsibility
for Douglas' safety as well?
Oh, with all due respect, ma'am,
he would not have needed to be saved
if he hadn't been in danger.
You're a difficult man
to impress, chief.
Sir, Petty Officer Douglas
was wounded badly.
It was not a time for enthusiasm.
For the moment,
put aside the fact that Lt. Rivers
changed the mission
and consider the events of the rescue.
- Can you do that?
- Yes, sir, I can do that.
What is your opinion now
of what Lt. Rivers did?
Do you know the first rule
of a SEALs team, sir?
Enlighten us, chief.
Never leave your man.
What are you saying?
Douglas was by himself
when we got there.
The lieutenant fired the flare
and then left.
With Culbertson on his back.
Yeah, but he
abandoned his man, sir.
All right, what if Lt. Rivers
stayed behind to help Douglas,
and as a result, the Undersecretary
Culbertson was killed?
That would be unfortunate.
But that rule exists for the sake
of undersecretaries everywhere.
Our bond
is what makes SEALs successful.
So Lt. Rivers seriously violated
the SEAL code?
How the hell do you...?
Admiral?
I'm here. We're running out of time.
What do you have?
Well, sir, apparently,
Rivers left Douglas alone
in the process of rescuing
Undersecretary Culbertson.
Oh, this is bad news, commander.
Well, he did it
to save Culbertson's life, sir.
It doesn't matter, major.
SEALs do what they do
because they can rely on each other.
The team is everything.
You never leave your man.
So we've discovered, sir.
So there's no one left to talk to.
We've gotten everyone's story.
Not everyone's.
Your version of the rescue,
lieutenant.
No evasions, no games, no crap.
Just straight talk, huh? Man to man.
I say what happened,
and you two dedicated lawyers,
seekers of the truth,
will take my word for it, right?
Well, that depends
on what you tell us.
- I figured as much.
- Sit down, lieutenant.
We're not done.
So here's what we know so far.
You're an irresponsible leader.
A Rambo who puts his men's lives
in danger.
Is there anything else
we should know?
If there is,
you better tell us right now
because, frankly,
we are tired of asking.
Good. Then maybe if you get
tired enough, you'll just go away.
After what happened to your father,
we understand
how you feel about lawyers.
You don't know anything
about me or what I do.
You don't have the right
to understand me.
Oh, I know you, Rivers.
You're a hard-assed mustang
with a chip on your shoulder,
using your father as an excuse.
I can do anything I want
because Seaman Edgar Rivers
was persecuted.
Stop it. Back off, lieutenant. Do it.
Good thing you got a woman
to protect you, commander.
Any time, any place, Rivers.
Are you stepping up to the plate?
I can handle anything you got.
I got the last day of hell week.
Why don't you put on greens
and join the party?
What?
So you can push me around?
You can handle anything I got.
All right, I'll go.
You tell me your story and I'll be there.
Are you serious?
You make it through the day,
I'll give you my biography.
Deal.
Commander.
I hope you're ready for this.
Welcome to the last phase
of SEAL training, commander.
You've been captured by the enemy.
Your task is a simple one.
All you have to do is survive.
Lawyers.
Is something wrong?
That old night blindness thing
acting up again?
That's what it indicates
in your service record, isn't it?
Crashed a Tomcat
on the carrier deck at night.
It's okay. Look at me.
What was the name of your RIO,
buddy, huh?
Was he a nice guy?
Was he your friend, huh?
He liked you, didn't he?
He trusted you, he had to.
He put his life in your hands.
The stupid sucker. It's clear.
How do you like
answering the questions now?
What do you think?
A lawyer with nothing to say.
You want to take a shot at me,
commander?
Lieutenant.
What?
Take it easy. You're supposed
to test him, not break him.
Anything else?
- Yeah. I'll get the corpsmen.
- You do that.
You know the secret of happiness,
lieutenant?
You can defeat the pain, Curtis.
It's all in your mind.
Or would you rather cash in
your chips and ring the bell?
Tell me everything.
- What you've heard is right.
- Stop stonewalling me.
I've got nothing to add.
Make something up.
Get out of here.
No, no, no, let's go.
Come on, come on, come on.
Tell me what happened.
Tell me what you heard.
You needlessly endangered
your men.
And you believe that?
Three of your team were injured.
Plus the hostage.
Anything else?
You broke the SEAL code.
You left your man.
Is it true?
I don't have to defend myself to you,
to them or to anyone.
The mission I took was to save
the Undersecretary of State.
I did that.
Why do your men resent you?
Resent me?
They hate my guts.
Why?
Because I operate instinctively,
regardless of their wishes.
They still follow you.
They have to. I outrank them.
It's not because...
They respect you.
You went back for Douglas?
Yeah.
You lit a flare so the others
would come find him.
Did Douglas tell you that?
He was unconscious.
Is that what he said?
Wasn't he?
Whatever.
Why won't you speak
on your own behalf, lieutenant?
Because all the medals in the world
won't make you a better leader.
Commander,
what happened to you?
It's a long story.
How are you feeling?
About the same.
- Depressed?
- A little.
- Bitter?
- What do you mean, sir?
Are you angry?
Feel you got a raw deal?
Some, I suppose.
Is that why you lied to me?
Sir?
You weren't unconscious
during the rescue, were you?
You're a lousy liar,
Petty Officer Douglas.
Probably not enough practise.
Try the truth.
The truth?
The truth is he gets nominated
for a medal.
And I get to be an invalid
for the rest of my life
because he couldn't wait.
You saw him pull Culbertson out.
You saw him kill the terrorists.
You saw him carry Culbertson
to safety, didn't you?
Yes, sir, I did.
So what?
Did Lt. Rivers abandon you?
He came over there.
I told him to get out of there,
get the hostage down to the beach.
He fired a flare to mark my position.
And when he saw our men
heading towards us, he left.
A minute later, the guys were there.
So he didn't abandon you?
No.
Maybe he deserves the medal,
I don't know.
But I wouldn't wanna serve
with him again.
I mean, not that I have
need to worry about that.
Lt. Rivers deserves the medal.
You deserve a little relief.
Let go of the anger.
Forgive the man
so you can get on with your life.
I won't forgive him.
But I won't lie anymore.
What are you looking for, sir?
I'm looking for a second eyewitness.
You got one.
Thank you.
Together on this day,
we offer a prayer for peace
and a tribute to those who defend it.
Together on this day,
we say thank you
to those who step forward to safeguard
our security and our ideals.
What better way
to express our gratitude
than by presenting this country's
highest military decoration for valour?
Mr. Undersecretary?
Mr. President.
For his conspicuous gallantry
and intrepidity
at the risk of his life above
and beyond the call of duty,
Lt. Curtis Rivers,
United States Navy, an American hero,
is hereby awarded
the Medal of Honour.
Your nation thanks you
and may God bless you.
Thank you, sir.
I would have followed you
anywhere.