"Perfect Day" playing
Just a perfect day
Drink sangria
in the park
And then later
When it gets dark,
we go home
Just a perfect day
You made me
forget myself
I thought
I was someone else
Someone good...
Chris's voice:
Another one burned last night.
Better than TV.
People outside the fence,
they took the last of them four days ago.
People just like us
run like cattle,
piled into trucks,
one suitcase apiece.
Headed east.
At least that's the rumor.
Bakersfield, Vegas,
who knows?
You just keep me
hanging on...
Chris's voice:
It's safe inside the fence.
Outside, everything's dead,
everyone's gone.
This is, uh, day nine.
Nine days since
the lights went out
and that fence went up
and our little green friends
moved in.
Soldier:
Let's roll!
Travis says
we're the lucky ones.
He'd throw those dudes a
parade if they'd let him.
And, look, we are grateful
to our saviors,
to the ones who protect us,
to those who know
when it's feeding time
at the zoo.
Turns out there's nothing you'll ever
take that nature won't take back.
It all belongs
to her again.
And the dogs
and the dead and the...
You just keep me
hangin' on
You just
keep me hangin' on...
Hello.
Hey, we have to repaint
the family room.
We did last week.
I know, it needs
a new coat.
Travis found some more
paint in the garage.
What's the point?
Semi-gloss.
What? Excuse me?
I mean, no one's coming
to the open house, Mom.
Market's taken
a bit of a turn.
I can still
see the stains.
Hey, you can see the ocean.
What? Still not on?
Oh, they probably don't want to
strain whatever's left of the grid.
Don't worry.
They're gonna
get it sorted.
Oh, my God.
- Where are you going?
- Huh?
Moyers, he's making
some kind of announcement.
He asked me to attend.
Well, we wouldn't want to upset him,
would we?
Okay.
- What's the problem?
- Uh, how much time do you have?
- Maddie...
- My house is a refugee camp,
my daughter's room is an
ICU unit for strangers.
- Someone has to cook, someone has to clean...
- Listen, calm down.
...someone
has to watch Nick.
- Well...
- And that someone, somehow, is me.
'Cause I don't know
where your ex-wife goes.
She's helping sick people.
Is this about Liza?
- What? No, it's about you.
- Me?
Yeah, you run off
to play man of the people...
- I'm not playing.
- ...with your soldier friends...
- This is not easy.
- ...and I could use a little bit of help here...
Stop. Oh, my God,
just stop it.
This domestic bickering
like it's normal,
like you're normal people
in a normal kitchen.
It's not normal. Stop it.
Stop acting like it is.
You ready to go?
Please.
Do it.
Come on, just do it.
Come on.
Chris, what do you
think you're doing?
- Get down here.
- Dad, you gotta see this.
Chris, now.
I want you
to help Madison, okay?
Okay, just look at this.
- I don't have time for...
- Just five seconds. Look.
There, you see that?
See what?
What am I looking at?
It's like a light
or a glint,
but they said there's
nothing alive out there.
Okay, come inside.
- Dad, I think there's someone out there.
- There's no one out there.
It's just the sun's caught
some reflection and...
You got to stop,
okay?
Come on.
I found this
on the counter.
Oh, yeah,
I guess I forgot.
Oh, you forgot?
Yeah.
I guess I did.
- Okay, here it is.
- Oh, no, thanks. I'm good.
I don't think
that's the best idea.
Well, I got to kick it.
That's the whole point, right?
Nick, come on.
- Nick...
- Look, give it to Griselda.
She needs it more than I do.
You said so yourself.
I know what I said,
but the point is to wean
you off of it slowly.
So it just doesn't,
you know, happen again.
I thought you'd be happy.
I am happy,
I just...
Okay, well, if you need it,
it's right here.
- Don't be a hero.
- No chance of that.
- Hey, Mom?
- Yeah?
Are you okay?
Enjoy your swim.
All right,
listen up here, folks.
As commanding officer
of this detachment,
I am proud to announce
that we are infect free
for a six mile radius
around this perimeter.
We are on the offensive.
The tide has
most definitely turned.
Yeah.
All right,
command asked that I read from the following.
"Be advised,
the DZ remains off-limits
while Hazmat teams dispose
of any bio-hazardous material."
Woman:
What bio-hazardous material?
Hey, I'm supposed to read this,
you're supposed to listen, okay?
Man:
When will you get the phones up?
"Anyone attempting
to compromise or circumvent
the perimeter of this camp
will be detained."
Man #2:
Are we being relocated?
Sir, this is a secure position,
so, no, you're gonna stay put.
"Curfew will remain in effect
until further notice.
The new health screening
policy will continue.
Sanitation, water treatment,
and other services will return
as we approach
total containment."
Sir, we need medicine.
What about that?
We are working on that.
"So keep boiling that water.
You will also find several iodine
tablets in your weekly rations."
Where are the people outside the fence?
Where did you move them?
Crowd:
Where? Where?
All right,
folks, listen.
You are in
one of 12 safe zones
south of
the San Gabriels, okay?
So you guys
are the lucky ones.
You guys... you get
to stay in your homes,
ride this thing out,
all right?
So, relax,
count your blessings, be nice.
So I don't have
to shoot you.
Yeah.
What's your name, miss?
Uh, Alicia Clark.
Oh, Clark.
Yeah, right here.
- Hi.
Ofelia Salazar.
Oh, could you
spell that for me?
S-A-L-A...
you're not even looking.
Oh.
Yeah, no, here it is.
Um, Ofelia.
- Mr. Manawa?
- Yes, sir?
Moyers:
A word, please.
Come on.
- Soldier: Have a nice day.
- Ofelia: Yeah, you, too.
Man: Just one case per family, ma'am.
That's how it goes.
Moyers: Guy who lives in this house
with the covered car, Thompson.
- Doug Thompson? Yeah.
- Yeah, okay.
So, he won't
do the screening.
And his wife thinks
for some reason
maybe you could talk
some sense into him.
Well, I don't
really know him.
We had a beer once,
and he showed me his car he's rebuilding.
You're a gearhead?
Well, I've kept my father's
Ford going for over 30 years.
Dude, 30 years! That is so great.
Can you help me or no?
- Well, it's just I don't really know the guy.
- Okay.
Okay, thing is here is I'm
trying to avoid a situation.
So either you're gonna go in
and you're gonna talk him down,
or I'm gonna go in,
I'm gonna take him down.
- Yeah or no?
- Okay.
Good.
Gloves on, let's go.
How long's
he been in there?
He was acting strange
yesterday,
and then
at dinner he, uh...
Maria, how long?
Since then.
Since dinner last night.
The soldiers wanted to talk to him,
but I thought...
I thought it would be better if
it was from someone he knew,
and he's liked you
so much, so...
Doug?
What's going on?
Hey, Trav.
You're worrying
your family, man.
I know that.
But I don't...
I don't think
I can do it.
Do what?
Take it easy.
They keep asking me
what's happening.
They keep asking me if
everything's gonna be okay
and I... I don't
have the words.
It is gonna be okay.
That's what you say.
That's all
that you have to say.
Will they know
that I'm lying?
Doug, your family
needs you.
Now.
They need you
to go outside that door
and tell that guard
that you're gonna be okay.
Show 'em
that you're okay.
That's all.
Yeah.
Hang in there, buddy.
Hey, handsome.
I got to go.
You have plenty of juice
for the night, okay?
Mm-hmm.
He's stable.
Morphine's helping.
You can't stay?
I made some soup.
Squash from my garden.
I have other people
to check on.
Please take some with you.
You must have seen a lot
of people like Hector.
At the hospital?
Yes.
Take it.
I don't know what
I would have done.
Hector is all I have.
Thank you.
Woman: Thank you, Liza.
See you tomorrow.
- Why show me that?
- Do you see it?
I mean, why not
show your dad?
I tried.
He just said it wasn't anything.
Well, maybe he's right.
It could just be a piece of metal or a window
or, you know,
I don't know.
Look, there's
a pattern, okay?
Someone's out there.
A human someone,
someone who needs our help.
We don't know that.
What else could it be?
Why else would it just...
If someone needs help,
they go to the soldiers.
Unless they can't.
Or they won't.
Do you see it?
Man on radio: 3-2 Echo,
this is Bravo Actual.
Standing by
for a sit-rep, over.
3-2 Echo,
this is Bravo Actual...
Don't you
have to get that?
They'll leave a message.
You're in my head
all day.
I can't concentrate.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait, wait, wait.
Maybe we should just
slow down a little.
Right.
Yeah, we should.
- I'm sorry. Are you upset?
- No.
No, it's okay.
I just...
I like you, Ofelia.
That's all.
Yeah, you're like
the only thing
that makes me believe there's
still good in people.
Hey, of course there is.
Hey, um...
did you get the medicine?
I tried.
I asked the corpsman.
What'd he say?
They got it all
locked down tight.
I guess they're
stockpiling
for the big push
to take the city back.
It's just, um, my mom's
really sick, so...
Yeah, I know that.
Man on radio:
3-2 Echo, Interrogative:
- Where the hell is my damn truck?
- I'm sorry.
Please advise.
Bravo Actual,
this is 3-2 Echo.
Finishing patrol.
Heading back.
Was that make-up sex?
We got to fight more.
Whoo.
Hey.
What's the hurry?
I thought that was nice.
- It was.
I got things to do.
Can't it wait?
Come here.
Come back.
What's going on?
I don't know.
There's no news
from anywhere.
Vivian said
she heard soldiers
talking about quarantine
camps out near Barstow.
I mean, I don't know.
She's a gossip, but...
No, I meant with you.
What's going on with you?
I mean,
you're buzzing around here all day every day,
driving yourself nuts.
I mean, you hover,
clean,
watch Alicia and Nick
like a hawk.
Nick needs
to be watched.
Yeah, I know.
Still.
Well, if we're exchanging
parenting tips,
you might want to pay
more attention to Chris.
Oh, okay.
I mean, all I do all day
is pay attention to...
Positive attention.
All right.
How come I feel like I'm being
called into your office?
Hmm?
I missed you.
He showed me the video
he took from the roof.
Jesus, that kid has got a world-class
imagination. You know that.
I saw it, too.
- I did.
- Yeah? Okay.
- What did you see?
- I don't know, like a... like a light.
- Mm-hmm.
- Like someone reflecting the sun.
Great.
So you saw a light.
What am I supposed
to do with that?
Go to Moyers and say, what?
"I... my kid saw a light,
so your soldiers, tell them
to drop their duties and..."
That is their duty. It's nine days.
What have they done?
They promised
medicine, doctors,
electricity,
information.
Where is it?
What about the phones?
- Don't you wonder why they can't get a landline?
- No, I don't wonder.
- Cell towers? Nothing?
- Maybe they got something bigger to worry about.
Well, maybe they don't
want the phones to work.
Oh, babe, are you listening to yourself?
You're talking paranoid.
I don't want to encourage this with Chris,
and you shouldn't either.
So you did see it.
Maria:
Travis! Travis!
- Travis!
- It's Maria.
Maria?
- What are you doing out? It's past curfew.
- They can shoot me.
- What's wrong?
- Doug's gone.
I was in the back of the house with the
girls and I don't know where he went.
All right, calm down, calm down.
Just breathe.
He's missing.
Okay, what did you say to him?
- I didn't say anything.
- He took his car.
He took his stupid,
precious car and I don't know where he went.
- Okay, let's take the girls inside.
- No, they stay with me.
Look, I'm sure he's fine. He's just
clearing his head somewhere, that's all.
We're not allowed to drive inside the fence,
Travis. It's not allowed.
I know, I know.
I understand.
So what... what if he...
oh, my God.
No, look, just don't go there,
please, all right?
I'm gonna find him.
I'll find your dad, all right?
We'll find him, yeah?
Come on, I'll walk you home.
Shit.
Ah, Christ.
I hooked it.
Travis:
His wife's worried he went over.
I'm just asking that you
send out one patrol.
- He hasn't been missing long.
- He's not missing.
We pulled Doug Thompson
last night.
Found him
up by the fence
bawling his eyes out
in his damn muscle car.
That guy, man, he is...
he's a head case.
Can't have that
around camp.
God damn it!
Don't look at me
like that.
It's not my order, though I agree with it.
You should, too.
You talked to the guy,
didn't you?
He seem okay to you?
- No.
So what are we
talking about?
Thompson gets the help
he so desperately needs
back at headquarters,
I don't have to worry about some
guy going psycho inside the fence.
That's a win-win.
You could've notified
his wife, sir.
I'm not a social worker.
That's your job,
Mr. Mayor.
Now, you go ahead
and notify away.
What?
My son, he saw a light
in the DZ
up on the hillside.
There's nothing alive out there.
He didn't see anything.
We, uh...
we went house to house, block by block.
I know.
- Forget it.
- Already did.
Oh, that's money.
Cynthia?
Liza, there you are.
Where's Hector?
Getting the care he needs.
Who are you?
I'm Dr. Exner.
Cynthia:
She's from the government.
Cynthia's told me
all about you.
Oh.
What did she tell you?
That you're the reason
why her husband's alive.
That you're
a very good nurse.
Cynthia:
Nurse practitioner.
That's basically
a doctor.
Where did you
take Hector?
Sit down.
I want to see him.
Cynthia was kind enough
to show me this chart,
and I'll admit I'm not
familiar with some of these...
Look, I should
explain this to you...
Cynthia,
do you mind if Liza and I speak privately?
Oh, no, no, no.
That's great.
Of course.
I should get
packed anyways.
Liza, you're an angel.
Oh...
Where's she going?
She wanted to be
with her husband.
Where is that?
You used a morphine drip.
Unorthodox.
I, uh... I didn't have
any nitrates,
so I had to salvage
from another neighbor.
I needed to find a way to get
the pressure off of his heart.
What about
your other patients?
I've already
met four people
that swear you're the
reason they're alive.
I'm just making them
comfortable.
Hector's
the only crit case.
Well, you did very well,
considering you're not actually a nurse.
Are you?
He was gonna die.
I didn't know what else to do.
I needed to get her
to trust me
so that she could
let me...
so that I can help.
It's all right.
Desperate times.
Perhaps you'd be willing
to pretend a little longer?
Excuse me?
Oh!
Ah!
It was under control.
I drained it.
We change the dressing
twice a day.
No antibiotics,
this was always the outcome.
It's not
anything you did.
We're gonna
take care of you.
- How are you gonna do this?
- We have a facility nearby.
- Military facility?
- It's military now, fortified.
We have beds, surgeons,
which, I'm afraid,
is what your wife's
injury requires.
My wife would like to know
how far this place is.
Close, 15 minutes.
Not a lot of traffic
these days.
I'm going with her.
Of course.
She's your wife.
Uh-huh.
- No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
Nick?
- Nick.
- What?
This is Dr. Exner.
Hi.
I understand you may
be in need of methadone.
Well, I would
love methadone
if I was trying to kick,
which I've already done.
When's the last time
you used?
Uh, I don't know.
When did the world end?
Couple of days
before that.
What's this?
Overdue house calls.
I'm Dr. Exner.
Oh, Travis.
Can't tell you how happy
we are to see you.
Um, is something
wrong with Nick?
Nick:
No, I'm fine.
But your ex-wife,
man, she's a NARC.
Told this lady I was the
neighborhood dope fiend.
98.6. I'm gonna check
your blood pressure.
So are you the one that decides
who goes to this facility?
Exner: Well,
I have some help, but, yes.
Like Doug Thompson?
I can't discuss
other patients.
Liza: Excuse him.
He worries about everyone else.
Your friend
is in good hands.
Just like Hector Ramirez.
Just like
Griselda will be.
You okay, Nick?
Yeah.
Uh, yeah, yeah.
Is Mr. Ramirez okay?
Congestive heart disease
is manageable.
Your heart rate's
elevated.
You're a very
attractive woman.
Daniel:
Where did you go?
Madison:
Outside the fence.
What did you see?
- Madison: Who is that?
- Daniel: That's the doctor.
She wants to take my wife
and do surgery on her.
Well, that's good.
Tell me what you saw.
Bodies.
Yes.
The infected.
But...
Go on.
There was a man
shot like the others,
like the rest,
but he... he wasn't sick.
And there were others
like that.
When I was young,
these men...
these men were
from the government.
They came to our town
and they took
some people away.
And my father
was someone
of certain importance
in the community,
so he went to speak
to the captain
and asked,
"When will they return?"
And the captain
told my father,
"Miguel, don't worry.
They always come home."
And they did.
I was standing
in the river fishing.
Just a boy.
And I found them.
All of them.
All at once.
All around me.
In the water.
My father told me not to
have hatred in my heart.
He said that men
do these things
not because of evil.
They do evil
because of fear.
And at that moment,
I realized my father is a fool
for believing
there was a difference.
If it happens,
it will happen quickly
and you must
be prepared.
Yeah, if what...
what happens?
I must go with my wife.
If I don't return,
you will look after Ofelia for me.
She's a grown woman.
She doesn't need...
Please.
You will look after
Ofelia for me, please.
Thank you.
Keep your son close.
What do you
want me to say?
You don't know.
What?
You have no idea.
Go away.
You gotta leave.
What the hell happened
to your face?
Knock, for Christ's sake.
Go away!
Stop, Nick, let me
just have a look at it.
Nick!
- Let me in.
- What's going on?
Let me in.
Nick. What happened?
Travis, stop, look.
Let me just...
I got it, okay?
Okay.
Alicia:
Nick, he's gone.
Come on, let me in.
Do you want me
to get Mom?
Who did that to you?
- Are you okay?
- Mm-hmm.
You want to talk
about it?
Hey, hey, it's okay.
It's okay.
Liza:
All right.
This is good,
this is good.
Okay, come on.
All right.
- Careful.
- Soldier: Okay, let's go.
- Liza: Gentle.
- Hey, I don't know how long we will be.
- Soldier: Let's go to your right.
- Okay.
What the hell
is going on?
- Liza: Gentle.
- Hey. Whoa, hey, hey. What's all this?
If we don't get Griselda to the surgeon,
she's gonna lose the foot.
- You're in the way.
- All right, okay.
All right, step. Good.
- Soldier: Here we go. Lead on.
- Liza: Okay.
- Sir, I'll need you to wait.
- Liza: All right...
No, that's okay.
That's his wife.
Come on, come on.
I have two names.
Griselda Salazar,
Daniel Salazar.
No, not you.
- Nicolas Clark.
- What?
Come on, man.
Free medical, care of the US Military.
Run.
- Travis: Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Hey!
That's a mistake.
No, no, that's a mistake.
- That's a mistake. Nick...
- Alicia: Wait. Hey! Hold on!
- Madison: No, no, no!
- Take it easy. Take it easy.
- Back off, sir.
- Don't you hurt him.
Stand down.
Stand down, ma'am.
- Madison: Nick!
- Come on.
- No, he's not sick.
- Calm down, ma'am.
Hey, hey, hey! Hey!
Travis:
Easy!
- Dad!
- Take it easy.
- Soldier: Step back.
- What are you doing?
Take it easy, man!
He's a kid!
It's an old man
and a kid.
What are you doing?
This is our home.
Hey, I didn't
do anything, man.
I didn't do anything.
Let Nick stay.
He's not a risk.
I'll look after him.
Please.
- You said you wanted to help.
- Yeah.
- I do, yes, but...
- Then get in the truck.
We could use you
in the hospital.
He knows me, please.
Just let me talk to Moyers.
It doesn't matter.
Travis:
Would you just let me talk to Moyers?
No.
No! No, Nick!
Soldier:
We're set!
Soldier #2:
Convoy's moving out!
I have a son.
He needs me.
We'll come back for your son.
He's safe here for now.
But Griselda, the others,
they need you.
I need you.
You coming?
- Soldier: Let's go!
- Soldier #2: What's the hold-up?
Exner:
Liza.
Soldier: Get her up.
Come on, lady.
Soldier #2: Come on, lady.
Are you coming or not?
Mom?
Don't worry.
All right, clear out.
Chris:
Mom.
Where is he?
Where did you take him?
No... Nick!
Chris?
Liza.
She did this.
Alicia's voice:
"Patrick, if you find this,
I'm sorry.
If you find this,
I love you.
I saw something today,
something that horrified me.
At first, I thought
it was unnatural.
I thought
it was an aberration.
But I was wrong.
What I saw
was prophesized.
What I saw was godly.
And I think it's overdue.
I wish you were here,
but I will see you soon.
And you will hold me."
Alicia's voice:
"If you find this, I am sorry."
"If you find this, I love you."