The Reincarnation of Sex
- You have a beautiful body.
- You too.
- Speak quietly.
- They are heavy sleepers.
Scares me.
Ok.
This makes it easy.
Antonio!
- You knew.
- Leave them.
Don't go there, don't go.
My daughter...
...with an employee!
I'll kill them.
They have their rights!
Rights?
I'll not let you go there.
- They have the right to do so?
- Yes.
And us?
And me?
Hi.
Let me help you.
Then?
Her monthly bleeding has come?
Here now.
Do you lie to defend this girl?
...what she wants and do.
...is law for you.
But we that know what is better for her.
She's not pregnant, if this
is what you want to know.
Lia. I want to talk to you.
Yes?
Do not need to serve
the lunch to Arthur.
I told him to go to
the city buy some tools.
He'll eat something over there.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Mom, what's happening with daddy?
Nothing!
Is something about Arthur?
No.
Come in.
I take you there.
Thank you Mr. Antonio.
Come with me.
What do you want Mr. Antonio?
I was thinking... you're my employee,
Patricia is my daughter and you sleep together.
I have the right to know.
Do you love each other?
Yes.
I know this story... money differences
disappear when is true love.
And your love is like this.
Yes, you don't are cheating.
We was waiting for a better time
to explain to you Mr. Antonio.
I had to do it!
I could not allow.
He crossed the line.
Daddy?
Is Arthur alright?
He's taking too long.
Maybe he has decided to
not come back anymore.
He was with your father's
money to shopping.
He can stay in the city
or travel to another place.
Maybe he had found a
girlfriend over there.
Patricia?
Yes.
Is too late now.
Your father wants to close here.
Daddy?
You are thinking on Arthur.
Sorry.
He's a betrayer.
I gave him everything, home, food,
my friendship, payment for his work.
He abandoned me!
I was already suspicious.
He was only waiting an opportunity
I put money on his hand and he left me.
Now i do not want listen nothing
about him in this house anymore.
Your mother is alright, he
is certainly with some woman.
Forget this guy
Patricia.
Come Patricia.
Your father Patricia.
He killed me.
With an ax.
I wish i could have your
whole body, but i can't.
How did she knows about everything?
I didn't tell you where.
Why?
You can't drink so much.
Patricia.
Ten years later.
- Mr. Fabio?
- Me, us.
- Did you come because the ad?
- Yes.
We'll marry and the house of
the ad looks very good to us.
Congratulations for your wedding.
- Thanks.
- Come to my office, we'll can talk privately there.
I'll show you some photographs. Green around,
fresh air and a good price for the rent.
No complications and with guarantee.
I'm sure we'll make a big deal.
The house is a palace.
Celia.
Celia
I want Fabio.
Fabio!
Yes.
Come in.
I need to finish this darling.
Let's go to bed.
I'm in the mood to make love.
- But now? Is too soon!
- Yes, let's go. Doesn't matter.
- I'm sweaty and dirty.
- Doesn't matter, let's go.
Celia
Celia, I'm tired.
I think sex is the best
thing in the world, you know.
But i have my limits, i'm tired
i'm so sorry.
Sorry? I came three times, you five and
you're not satisfied yet. It's enough for me.
Ok, i'll not force you anymore.
I worked all day my love.
Allright, i'll control myself.
Is a nice house.
I couldn't choose a bad estate agent.
I knew that i could trust on you.
Celia.
Your body.
Your skin.
Feel the pleasure.
Enjoy.
Masturbate.
Enjoy the pleasure
I did the right thing fixing the car.
Is ok now.
What do you want Mr. Antonio?
I was thinking...You're my employee, Patricia
is my daughter and you sleep togheter.
Stop the car.
What? Stop the car!
Are you ok? Yes, i'm fine.
You look nervous, i
can take you to Roberto.
I'm not needing a psychiatrist.
Roberto is your uncle and a
excellent doctor, he can help you.
I do not have any problem,
i'm ok. I'm not going crazy.
I'm just worried. Don't be worried.
Ok.
Celia what's happening?
Celia? Do you hear me?
Don't let's talk now.
Let's fuck a lot.
Fuck me, fuck me now.
Yes, like this.
I want you inside me.
More, more.
Hello Roberto? Is Fabio.
Listen me and do not talk. The honeymoon?
Is nice. the new house is wonderful.
Everything is alright, but Celia...
What's happening?
She has being weird.
Another day she gone into the bush like a robot,
hypnotized. Looking for something that only she could see
having high sex drive, anxiety
and dificulty breathing.
Now she wants sex all the time.
Is a hysterical and sick behavior
I want that you come to visit us.
Ok Fabio.
Don't worry, i know how to get there.
Give me more information about Celia
I feel her heart beating abnormally when we have
sex, I try to stop but she always wants more and more.
And never be sastisfied. Another day i felt that
she would stab me if i had insisted to call you here.
Fabio?
Hello?
Did you call uncle Roberto honey?
I listened everything.
You don't need to hide.
You're wrong saying i'll stab you.
Now he'll come here to hear me and give me medicine. But he could
be here to do another thing... Doesn't matter he is my relative.
Me in the middle, you
behind, him in the front
I'll go crazy fucking with two men.
Take it easy. Stop with this.
The knife Celia, the knife.
Take the knife
Celia take the knife. Kill kill kill.
Enjoy, enjoy, enjoy Celia.
Enjoy everything.
This way, this way.
Celia? Fabio?
Are you there?
Go away.
Mr. Antonio.
Only now i found a tenant to your house.
She don't know about the tragedy
that occurred in the house.
She is a weird woman but
the family pay for the rent
I hope you understand that
wasn't possible to find a couple.
But we know our new tenant will not be without
man in that lonely place for too much time.
The house was rented for a good price.
Ligia.
You're so lonely.
You need love.
The road Lidia. The road.
A man, Ligia a man to love.
Any man Ligia, anyone.
- You'll not regret.
- I can't be here too long.
You'll want to stay.
I have to deliver a shipment
in the city tomorrow morning.
We'll fuck just once,
very fast, and i 'll go ok?
Don't speak.
Wait and you'll see.
What a big house!
Do you like it?
Cool.
Come on let's go.
Do you want something to drink?
Whisky, martini?
I'll drive! Only the bed and fast.
And music?
No. Only the bed and be fast.
- Ligia, undress!
- I have time to go
i'm getting nervous.
Delicious!
I do anything you want
I do not like men, i like women
they smell good, soft skin.
Because of this i could not live in the
city, my family discovered everything
I couldn't stand
I'm struggling with this now,
i'll like they could see me now.
They could understand my effort.
Come.
I'll get along.
You're so cold, Ligia.
Try.
I need a body, Ligia.
A man's body.
Shit!
Fuck!
What's happening?
Don't go, don't go.
Shit! Let me go!
I'm not a woman.
I don't have pussy
I know what you want. You
want to rub in a pussy!
So go finger fucking. Nobody will
listen you. Go finger fucking. Shit.
I do not know what this
fucking bitch is thinking.
I could be in the city now.
Shit! I'm belated again.
This always happens
with me, fucking shit!
Oh no.
Fuck!
Hello
Ana Maria?
Yes.
Ligia?
I want to see you.
You ran away without tell where
you was going. You disappeared.
Leaving us.
Are you sure that you
really want to see me?
I miss you!
- I was with a man here.
-  A man? - Yes, a man.
- You are so versatile, but do you liked?
- I don't know, we did not fuck.
I was confused and the guy became
furious and said to me go finger fucking.
He was a trucker.
This is so ironic.
Stupid.
- Your isolation is dangerous.
- What do you mean?
Is dangerous for me
I want to take you back,
let's live together.
I don't care about your family.
I don't want to waste more time.
We need more liberty.
Let's live with who undertand us.
This place is not bad.
Yes i know.
Is good to be in isolation.
But what we did here could be
done in my place in the city.
We have food delivery there.
It would be great, but i think
i'm beginning to like this place.
Ok, let's spend your parent's money on
this rent. I can come and go any time.
I'll let you with good companion. So you'll
not wish to go around and find someone.
I'm so curious to know what it is.
Ta - da ....
- A vibrator.
Yes.
A guarantee of fidelity,
better than any male.
No weight, no sweat, and no
hair to irritate your skin.
Is just to introduce and turn on.
You have an higienic and easy
orgasm because is just you that cum.
Let's try it?
I can do a free demonstration for you.
No, let's do the opposite
I'll stick on you.
Like if we were man and woman.
Suck this.
Hold it tight, i want to try
I want know how it would be
Patricia
do not allow this.
Do not allow, Patricia.
Do not allow.
Terminate with this.
Hold tight Patricia.
Stronger.
She's dying.
Come in.
Hi, are you lost?
No, i live near here
I'm home alone.
Do you want a lift?
Yes
I like of you
i never had someone like you.
You turn me on.
Wide open
I'll get inside of you.
Everything is inside, move now.
Ligia, i need this body
I need, Ligia.
Come on!
Kill him.
Give me the body.
It's my chance.
Make me vibrate, make me cum.
Cool.
Kill him, give me.
You'll not take him.
Don't dare me, Ligia.
Don't dare me.
More, do not stop now.
Take me, take me away
I warned you, Ligia.
Feel your heart.
It will explode.
Takes me.
What is that?
Stop stop stop
I want you.
Fuck!
Good grief!
I warned you, Ligia, i warned.
Good grief, this woman is crazy!
Good grief!
He witnessed everything, a judge determined an inquiry in the house.
The papers published what happened and we cannot rent the house.
This scientist is
investigating the house.
The police relatory do not satisfy him.
He said wasn't the madness that
made Celia kill her husband.
And Ligia did not have
heart related problems.
He had access to the autopsy.
Celia is my niece
I want to know what made her insane.
She's in an asylum now.
Saying things about psychic influences
about a head and a potted plant
that forced her to kill her husband.
The potted plant.
A girl named Tatiana said
more people was in the house
Ana Maria, a Ligia's friend.
A scientist can't do
nothing about what happened.
What happened, Mr. Antonio?
It's not the house.
We bought the house
ten, eleven years ago.
Myself, my wife Lia and my daughter
Patricia came from the country side
and employed a person
from the neighborhood
he helped me with the reconstruction
of the place. Arthur was poor
one night when i waked up
i discovered that him and
my daughter were having sex
I couldn't stand that situation
and i killed him on the road.
You don't belive me, sir?
It's why, Lia, my wife,
drunk until death too.
Because of what i've done.
My crimes...
His severed head is over there.
No decomposition.
It emits vibrations
and forces the people.
Come on, let's go!
Shit! Fuck this rain!
Is an abandoned place.
Enjoy
Mario.
Fuck.
We have to keep this joint burning.
You're burning me.
Gimme this shit.
What is this?
Leave him.
Son of a bitch.
What's happening here,
fuck! You're burning me.
Faggot.
You bitch!
Patricia, finish this.
What's happening, who's knocking?
Come here.
Are you crazy? you're hurting
me. Leave me alone. Fuck!
Leave me.
Stop with this, stop!
Fuck!
Are you crazy?
You're alright. What are we doing?
Crazy, man.
Step behind.
Did you get a thrill?
Let's get away from here
I also hade to escape.
Please go there Doctor, and prove.
Do you belive in that old man?
I do not know.
He doesn't know if it was 10, 11
or 12 years ago he bought the house.
He's sclerotic
i'm surprised, a
scientist with many doubts.
But we have some evidence.
What evidence, the deaths?
Your friend's disappearance?
There is much evidence of the
craziness of all these people.
That old man is in the
right place, a hospice.
But we need more, isolation he needs.
And Ligia? Her family do
not want to see her anymore.
They know she will
die, die of depression.
Doctor.
Is Ana...?
How do you know?
Her hair clip.
Call the police. I'll go to the house.
This story....
There is a dead woman's
body here, burned.
Maybe we'll find more bodies, and
because of this you'll call the police.
If i believe or not in what
that old man said is my problem.
Here, give this to her.
Come with us, you'll
prove nothing going there.
No.
You can't manage that.
Go faster.
Is not necessary.
He can be in danger.
No, and i hope you not
believe in this bullshit
I shouldn't have let him go there.
Is my house.
What do you mean?
I did an agreement with that old man, the
house is mine since i always rent it to someone.
Stop the car.
Let's have a break, Roberto will understand
how this is ridiculous and back out.
He'll not arrive to the house.
Stop! I want go out of the car!
Are you crazy?
Wait.
Go there doctor, see the pot
and prove i'm saying the truth.
My...
...car...
...is here.
Police!
It's him.
Stop, if you move i'll shoot.
He is in the trap, we caught him.
Celia what are you doing
here? You should be in ...
They are over there with Fabio.
We got married just few years ago.
He shouldn't have done this.
You did not go to our wedding party
I searched for you,
and i did not find you
I was very sad.
He is dead.
Dead?
Come here, come.
We're waiting for you.
We're in a new kind of therapy. The free
love in the marriage, or just the free love.
She wants to fuck you.
And i want you to fuck her.
Did you never imagine fucking my wife?
You will be the world's first stupid uncle.
Because nieces are
always delicious, hot.
Bring her here and let's make love.
Yes, an orgy.
Let's make an orgy, because the family
that fuck together will be always together.
Ghost! Hahaha!
I will kill you.
You're trapped
Patricia will finish everything.
You can't.
She just finished with
all the corrupted people
Patricia.
He'll not accept you after this.
Everybody was without hope,
distorted and corrupted ones.
She died to help me.
She can't.
Our dream.
No, do not listen.
Is the essence.
Don't pay attention.
Listen what i say.
Useless demagouge.
Lies!
Truth, you'll know.
Listen.
Your brain and your science will remain.
Your body and your nature will disappear.
Will be mine!
Son of a bitch!
Now, Patricia.
Protect the girl.
Let's go there.
Ok, boss.
He's dead. His head was cut off.
He is dead.
His head.
This girl is crazy,
there's nothing here.
In the living room.
Yeah, i think she is really crazy.
The doctor succeeded.
I tried to avoid the
police to go to the house.
That girl, Tatiana, ruined everything.
She told about her friend, told
about the recorder, told everything.
This is the end of our agreement.
I don't want to be the owner of the
house anymore. They are here outside.
Doesn't matter.
CINEMAGEDDOM